آقای چانگ
چه خبر؟
I would like to tell you I enjoy your
lecture very much
ممنون
This is my phone number
هر پنجشنبه شب
My parents would go out for a
bridge game
اگه وقت کردی سر بزن
و به من خوندن لوتوس طلایی رو یاد بده
من مدرس‌ام، اصول خودمو دارم
حیف شد!
The Golden Lotus and principles
don't mix
می‌تونی به روحم توهین کنی
ولی نمی‌تونی به روح پاکم توهین کنی
اون هنوزه دانش‌آموزه
چطور می‌تونه هرزه باشه؟
چی؟ هنوز برای شام نیومده خونه؟
Tell him to forget about getting
a car loan from me
Ching and I will stop by China Town
for some candies
هی، مگه هنوز باید بریم چایناتاون؟
من باید دوستم رو مرکز شهر ببینم
If ever you've kids, teach them to
respect their elderly
I'm in a rush, you knows
She's been waiting sometime
Did you pay your respect...
...to your mom's grave?
کردم، ۱۱ آوریل
April 11?
مگه ۱۱ آوریل عید پاک نیست؟
فکر کردی عیسی مسیح مادرته؟
Jesus
Christ
When I was dating your aunt
I dreamt about her every night
Have you dream about your
Miss Prefect yet?
نه!
Do you know how to pick the
perfect wife?
How?
I'll teach you a way
Which I learnt from my father-in-law
OK, when we sit down for lunch
in a minute
See if she would say Bon Appetite to
everyone
If she shows such a respect
That would prove her sensitivity
That means she can easily adapt to our
Chinese custom
Know how to respect our daily life
ritual
Understand?
She's no good...
...if she wouldn't even say
'Bon Appetite'
Hey, your father-in-law's got a point
And that's how I felt into the trap
الو، میام دنبالت
کجا داری میری؟
زود برای شام برمی‌گردم
خدای من، پاهام بی‌حس شده!
عجله کن!
Michael and I are working for the
U.S. Government
Teaching is only a cover-up
We grew up together
I witness Michael marry
and witness him divorce
His whole life is being dragged down by
gamble
This time, we're going to save a member
of Yamagushi
His name is Yamanmoto
He is very useful to C.I. A
I've done much for the US government in
these few years
But every time after work
I feel awkward
As if the feeling of glory is lacking
Do you think any bonus for
taking out the 'Jap' this time?
Why don't you ask the chief?
I hope so. I'm short of cash
To get laid?
Fuck off! You mean I have to pay to
get laid?
Joe, get ready!
I see that car coming!
You ex-girlfriend has the heart for me
these days
Crazy Susan?
She even gave me a ring
You meant she has money to buy you a
ring?
Sure, from the dough that you left her
Hell, with it, using my money
That's no big deal
Your money ends up anyways
You want her back?
نه thank you, it was hard working getting
rid of her
نهw that she has the heart for you,
she's all yours
You can have her back
You fucking stupid Joe, always cutting
so close
What do you think you're doing?
Fucking asshole
You better put on a good show
Back off! Fucking Chinese! Fuck you!
Mike, take off your pants
He dares not do it, come on
You must be crazy
You caught my car
Why are you talking here?
You fucking stinky bastard!
Go check.
خفه شو
Joe, Japanese is in the second car
Hey, in there, heh...
Mike
Put down your weapon!
I said put down your weapon!
Move! Move!
Drop your fucking gun
خفه شو
Try it man and he is history
Hey! I said back off!
What! You want him dead?
I don't care!
Yamamoto San. It's OK
OK, you're safe
We're from the U.S. Government
U.S. Government? بله
You have six
I have six
We're even
Alright, the job's all down
So let's go
چه اتفاقی برات افتاده عمو بیل؟
He mumbled other woman's name
when he was napping
I decided to wake him up with my fist
Woo!
Bon Appetite Dad, Bon Appetite Mom
Bon Appetite Jeff, Bon Appetite Josephine
Bon Appetite Jeff, Bon Appetite Gary
Bon appetite Josephine
Bon Appetite Uncle, Bon Appetite Aunt
Josephine eat rice
بزنیم تو رگ! / بیایید غذا بخوریم!
خداحافظ! مراقب خودت باش!
The aim we send you to China
Is to steal a national treasure back to
the U.S. A
چی؟
من یه چینی‌ام!
You're asking me to steal a national
treasure out of China?
Do you remember?
You've made an oath that you'll be
loyal to the Government?
As soon as you arrive at China
A man called Tong Ling will met you
He'll arrange everything for you
I heard that he is very cautious
And his background is complicated and
confidential
According to our information, he's
arranged
Many extremists escape from China
How about Michael?
Michael? I'll arrange him to meet you
In Taiwan when the proper time comes
موفق باشی!
YEAH! YEAH!
A new job was offered to me in China
چی؟
You don't even know how to speak
Putonghua
I am your mandarin tutor
Our first lesson is about social life
Do you have any questions?
My telephone number
Call me please!
Wow! You've been dreaming a lot!
Today
Our topics of discussion is
Courtship
It hurts, Ow, Ow, Ow...
Of course it hurts, you know why?
Why?
Because you finger's bigger than banana
Banana?
I have to go!
خداحافظ!
How come nobody would fit this ring?
Bye! Bye!
Welcome to China, آقای چانگ. I'm Tong Ling
Please to meet you
My pleasure!
After the revolution
The standard of living has improved
With restaurants and entertainment
spots everywhere
Some places are even better than
the west
But if it is as good as you describe
Why are so many people leaving?
What did you say?
Why are you laughing?
Where die you learn such fluent Mandarin
I have a special tutor
But I also speak Cantonese
Any which way you prefer
Hope our Chinese-American relationship
works well
It would be there best!
Like making sail in the favorable wind
You may talk to me in Cantonese
In Beijing, I've to curl my tongue
In order to speak Putonghua
Maybe God punishes my bad mouth
نه
You shouldn't be so superstitious
My car always break down
Needs repair from time to time
It seems that I have worser luck
These rural people are very poor
They don't have good food like you have
in the states
Don't push yourself if it doesn't suit
your appetite
As a matter of fact, the Americans are
flexible
You pay what you get
You eat the whole corn
while we eat popcorn
We eat buckets of popcorn at movies
Is there rice?
Please help yourself, eat more
ممنون
Does it suit your appetite?
When I had my training in Bangladesh
Even though the food was inevitable,
I just ate
The old lady wants you to have these
2 eggs
ممنون!
Have you ever consider leaving China?
I thought of it everyday
Why don't you leave then?
I stay to help the ones who really want
to leave
It is more meaningful this way!
The water still taste so fresh!
Get out of the car!
It is 140 bucks in total!
Are you sure?
The meter reads a hundred
Do I look like nerd, eh? $140?
Such a Con?
You've gotta pay for the luggage too!
نه point of arguing, pay according to
the meter
The sign says a dollar per kilometre
And two bucks more per luggage
4 bucks for 2 pieces, you dare say
forty bucks?
Right
Each luggage has travelled 20 kilometres
So two pieces would cost forty
There's no mistake, pay now!
نه sweat, pa
I'll handle it myself!
What are you doing?
Come over here
I don't have Chinese currency
But I have a thousand dollar bill
And another fifty dollar bill
You pick one yourself
I'll take this one
What a sissy wimp
If not for the money
I would never take you to Shaolin Temple
I'll bet this for a hundred R.M. B
It only worth 40 bucks
What are you talking about?
What a nerd!
A thousand yen can only exchange forty
R.M. B
I would never ever go inside
Shaolin Temple
You're pretty smart
Arrange for me to hide out at the
Shaolin Temple
So nobody would know
I am very careful indeed
The master is my neighbor
Just inform him if you need to see me
Have a seat while I go find him
Someone has sneaked into the
Assembly Hall
The door is opened, let's check inside.
Let's go
Come out!
How dare you sneak into the
Assembly Hall? Out!
Don't!
Who is this?
Don't move, your heart is beating so fast
How do you know?
Your pulse tells me so
Hey, I've seen every woman
And this girl causes my heart to run
What the hell is going on?
Come out!
Don't worry, I won't betray you
Go
Gentlemen, let's talk
من بی‌گناهم
Hey, don't let the other one get away
تنهام بذار
Don't come closer or else you will be
sorry
کمکم کن!
Hm, your steps are not bad!
Show me some more
Come, dance up!
Be careful!
You're right
I have the gun, so be careful
Who the hell was that?
You little fat ass!
دست‌ها بالا
Ah! You Shaolin monks
do like to attack from behind?
You don't know the way to hell, eh?
How dare you?
Attack from behind again
Weapons are prohibited at Shaolin Temple
For the time being, I'll keep the gun
for you
And who are you anyway?
Again?
I'm sorry
He is Abbot Hung-Chi of Shaolin Temple
This girl has mental problem
Her sickness, is healing fast
If she escapes
It would waste all their effort
Most of the people here speak Cantonese
Treat yourself like home
Help out here and there if you are free
Never leave the temple at daytime
Never leave your room at night
Eat while you may
Shit while you can
آقای چانگ, lf you happened to need some
foreign exchange
Please come to me immediately
Because, we set out rate slightly
different from outside
We're a few percentage higher. بله
استاد wants me to see if you have any
laundry?
Are you still mad at me?
استاد said the world should be
filled with
Peace, harmony, respect and love
So if I am still mad at you
I would break the rule of forgiveness
Those were your master's teaching
What about yourself? Me...
Monks don't lie
You should be angry at me
I would be if I were you
This is for you
A token of my apology
You know what this is?
Gameboy computer game
Have you played before?
Never
But I saw it in the supplementary
classes
What is this supplementary class?
Basically we studied history and
geography
And also new products of the world
استاد says we monks
should also learn modern things
Like?
The most expensive watch is "Swatch"
Karaoke is the hottest entertainment
There are four pope kings in Hong Kong
Dr. Martin is better than Nike
I can tell from your clothes, that you
are not trendy at all
You are not wearing Calvin Klein
نهt even a pair of 501
And no Giorgio Armani
How can you hang around town without
basic gear?
What do you mean?
To hit the town and stay cool, dude!
Uncle
Is this Gameboy really for me?
Do you know how to play?
نه problem
I'll study it. That's no problem
Be kind, be kind
شب بخیر, شب بخیر
ممنون... خواهش می‌کنم
Byebye, ByeBye
شب بخیر
اسم‌ت چیه؟
Priestling Grasshopper
I'll let you cry till you drop
HEY!
I shouldn't be treating you nicely
After what you've done to me today
I have no bad intention
It's OK, I know they haven't cooked
anything for you
I brought you two eggs
Come over and eat
I don't want it
You don't need to be so sad even if you
don't eat
I'm not sad
It you're not sad, what's the crying for?
I don't know
Maybe it is because of the snow
Are you kidding!
Do you have a radio here?
You should listen to music
In order to loosen up
I don't have music here
Maybe I can sing a song for you to relax
I am singing now
You want me to sing you five songs?
I can't remember that many
How about three?
You are so greedy!
I'll sing you one first!
La, La, La...!
Are you alright?
حالم خوبه
I heard something coming from the
backyard
I'll come visit you tomorrow night
اسم‌ت چیه؟
Jeffery!
چی؟ Fatty?
نهt Fatty, the name is Ching
The name is Ching
بیا تو
Hi!
You come from the States?
Morning, comrade استاد
Would you tell me...
Grasshopper
All the monks gone crazy this morning?
نهbody speaks a word
What's the matter! Tell me
We have to meditate these two days
So nobody is allow to speak
Don't tell anyone you saw me
I know you would come
I have something to show you
The right hand side
I'll come in and talk
Hey! Your room is locked!
I can't open the door without keys
How did you come out yesterday?
بلهterday, I stole the key while they
delivered meal
You've stayed here for a long time?
Almost 2 months
Where did you live before?
I don't know
Everytime I wake up I change room
Wait a second
You don't even know where you live?
You really don't know?
They've changed my room constantly
I don't even know where I am
Do you want to see what I paint?
How are you going to show me?
You only need to place your hand
against the door
Just concentrate and you will get it
Concentrate
Control your mind and your thoughts
اسم‌ت چیه؟
عجله کن!
Abbot told me yesterday
you're healing fast
You should concentrate on your health
instead
Don't waste other people's effort
Do you hear me?
روح!
Hey! Did you get it?
Are you still outside?
Kung-Chi, Kung-Chi.
Kung-Chi
I want to find your استاد
There is ghost in Shaolin Temple!
Don't bother with this
Stop this silly sound! It's so annoying!
OK! Be silent
I know...
today is the silent day in
Shaolin Temple
However... Quiet
You dare to stab on me
I accuse you murdering
I have to see Tong Ling
I have to see Tong Ling!
Talking is prohibited during
meditation day
I have to see Tong Ling...
Abbot, are you fine? حالم خوبه
He can't move in four hours
Let's eat
Why don't he show up tonight?
My feet...
A hot shower would be perfect to
loosen up
Talk about perfect timing!
Monks should not cunning, but he has
created troubles
Hey! What do you want?
I should say what do you want?
How come you didn't tell me
there is no hot water
I'm glad I haven't used soap yet,
or else.
Where is my shampoo!
It's right here
ممنون
What is your under arm?
نهthing, just some abscess from a tumor
Abscess? Must be poisonous
You better be careful
استاد
استاد, what happen to you
Do you want vomit?
Wow! So is that super natural power?
کجا داری میری؟
To the Market
Oh! It's you again, the Canton man!
So you speak Cantonese
So what? Tough!
You'll have to pay double to ride in
my cab
What a con!
I don't want to ride with you anymore
I won't let you ride either, tough luck!
You think I don't have a car? Tough?
What's the big deal? Tough shit!
To the train station, thanks
I'm not going, tough luck! Why?
How about I think you are ugly?
رئیس
Is there any books on super
natural power?
Please take a look over there
You want this?
Mom, I want the ball
I want the ball
نه, be a good child
Put the ball back
We have to go home now, let's go home
رئیس, I need a prostitute
A whore?
Sir!
رئیس Chang!
آقای چانگ, let me introduce to you
Miss Blossom
Listen, you better entertain آقای چانگ
well
Of course! This is for you
Thank You!
Do you have Calligraphy brush?
What! You want me to practice
Calligraphy?
We are police
Is someone looking for a whore?
Where is the man?
He left already
He left? What were you two doing?
He paid me for practicing Calligraphy
I never be a whore, mother fucker!
This is the happiest experience ever
happened
The man has class
Hey, my bike!
Stop it, it's a new bike
همون‌جا وساط
Why are you riding my bike, your crazy
bastard, stop it
Stop
Let's go, I say start the car
I'll charge you three times more
It's you? Why don't you just rob a bank?
Four times more
Shit!
It will be five times more if you
keeping on bargaining
Alright
You fucking bastard. Swearing'll cost
you $2 surcharge
My dearest, please start the car
There's more like it
Son of a bitch
Look what I bought you?
استاد asked me to return this to you
Who'd beaten you like this
It's the other senior colleagues
Why did they beat you up?
Monks shouldn't be indulged in
materialistic hobbies
And not to get in touch in these things
Grasshopper!
I have to go
Let's go
It hurts eh! Be quick
Grasshopper
You can't go
What's the problem with playing these
game
I thought you say Shaolin needs to
match modern pace
We must follow
our استاد's teaching
Everything is استاد's teaching
Have you got brains?
This game is lifeless but your brain
is alive
Playing well doesn't mean indulgence
آقای چانگ, teaching Shaolin pupils is my
responsibility
نهt yours
I've told you before that
Everyone in Shaolin Temple understand
Cantonese
How come you have to speak your mixed
Cantonese Mandarin?
Your Mandarin are poor, you thought you
can get away
Curling your tongue, pretending to be
standard Beijing Mandarin
consulting with a humble attitude.
Grasshopper
Since my Mandarin is marked as 'poor'
Your Mandarin must be perfect
Why don't you teach me?
I'm more than qualified, I welcome your
challenge
But I'm busy tonight
Good your night. Fuck you!
ممنون! I'm sorry
That's OK! I'm sorry
خواهش می‌کنم
It's you! چه خبر؟
I've something to discuss with you
But you have to help me out first
Where did you steal the keys from?
I stole it when they delivered the rice
You'd tell me earlier, I've wasted my
efforts to steal these
1,1,1,2,3,4,5,6,7
You look normal, don't seem to have
mental disorder
Who told you I have a mental problem?
But why are you here if you don't have
a problem?
I don't know the answer either
I woke up and found myself here
Even the people from the research
institute disappeared
The research institute?
What kind of research?
Supernatural power
You have supernatural power?
I don't know
But I know
what I have a powerful source within me
But I need another body to reinforce it
Like the other morning
you got the egg through the door
I don't understand what you're saying
You don't understand, eh?
Do you believe in the secret power of
crystal?
Sure, a lot of scientist all across the
world
Have experiment on crystal forces with
success
Right, I'm similar to crystal
I need a mediator to reinforce this
power
You don't believe me? Give me your hand!
Just concentrate
you can make your wishes come true
Really?
You want money? Don't even think
about it!
Can you turn my fist
to as big as a pot?
Sure, just concentrate
Are you sure? Of course!
Start!
Just concentrate
What are you thinking of just now?
نهthing, I thought of my nursing maid
just now
You have to concentrate. You too
Hey! It still doesn't work
You don't have to be that loud
OK! I'm sure about it this time
Are you sure!
Why am I hearing so clearly now?
Stop laughing, would you?
Wow! Bigger, bigger...
Wow! It's really bigger than a pot
You're really something!
Even Rocky can't beat me now
It's shrinking, shrinking!
It's spectacular
Hey! Wait
Can you make this blossom? Sure!
Of Course! OK!
Let's start
Blossom
I want to see a lot of flowers
So Many, many, many... flowers
Blossom...
Gees! Why isn't this working?
Tell me, why isn't this working?
Really beautiful!
A lot of people had said praises like
this before
But I usually do not admit
You know sometimes one has to be humble
But if you don't admit, people will say
you are sarcastic
Cantonese would describe a man handsome
They often do that
Do you think I am handsome?
What do you mean?
Me, handsome!
Who is it?
It's you! Grasshopper
Why did you dress yourself with flowers?
Take a look at your hat yourself
چی؟ My hat?
Who is it?
You bring her with you, I'll distract
them
Go
My legs are numb
I'll carry you
استاد, استاد
What is it?
استاد, I saw a walking flower pot
چی؟ A walking flower pot?
Are you crazy?
I really saw it
We'll split into three teams, let's go!
Grasshopper
Move it
Don't run!
Over there! They are behind the
bamboo sheet
The flower is over here!
I think I heard Grasshopper's voice
They are in front
Let's go!
Close your eyes quickly!
You want to kill me!
Hey! Why are you blocking my sight?
I can't see at all
Do you still remember how you get
the egg
This is our last chance
Quick, run, run...
Hey, what did you see?
آقای چانگ and Ms Mei fly up to the sky
Stupid, how could human being fly?
Shit! Miss Mei!
Come with me!
How can human being fly!
شب بخیر! Wait!
Are you coming tonight?
I'll let you know tomorrow
Hey! What's the matter? نهthing, go
I saw them flying together yesterday
چی؟
What did you see?
I thought I saw Chang Ching...
You're always not sure. It must be him!
Let's get him
Come out
Abbot, why are you short of breath
ha ha ha. You are short of breath too
I should be the only one who should be
short of breath
I dreamt of being chased by a chicken!
A chicken?
استاد, استاد... I lost him!
You stupid, the chicken is gone already.
Let's go!
Why are you so early this morning?
I come out whenever I want to
Why do you have black circles under
your eyes?
I didn't sleep well last night
You must be thinking of me last night!
I brought a friend to see you
Oh! Lt's you, uncle Bill, Why are you here?
I come to tell you
Are you dreaming?
Just tell her if you really like her
I'm dreaming? If you are not dreaming
You must be out of your mind
Look at her just like a floating cloud
If she is a cloud, what am I?
You are a bird
You should hand around the cloud
It makes sense?
When you are in heat, dirty mind is
hard to beat
Speak!
Do I look like a bird?
Oh my dear little white cloud!
Do you love this bird?
Little white cloud!
I love you, I love you
Please don't leave me!
Hey! What are you doing!
Are you crazy?
Oh! I'm just having a dream
Mr Tong, why are you so early?
You've got black eyes? Didn't you sleep
well?
You're right
I was up thinking about you the entire
night
Why are you thinking of me?
There's something I need to say to but
don't know how
You better think twice before you
say it.
Do you know...
Last time, when you left Shaolin Temple
alone
You were followed by secret police
Do you know that this action of yours
Would possibly get us all killed!
I remember when I was a kid
My family was really broke
There was once when I queue up for rice
And saw a man who jumped the queue
He was then beaten dead by the others
From then onwards
I knew the result of not following the
masses
Otherwise will end up like that man
You Americans are so lucky
You don't need to queue up for rice
But please remember
You're now in China
You have to follow the rules!
آقای چانگ
استاد wants you in the Monkey Temple
Grasshopper
Is anyone else in the backyard with you
last night?
Still that tough, huh?
Spank him again!
Tell the truth
Or else five more spanks
Again!
Get back up there, quick!
استاد, I'm finished!
I ask you again
Is there somebody else except you?
I... l...
Tell us the truth
استاد, it's painful
Tell me or there will be more pain
The truth
Spank again!
Stop it!
آقای چانگ, its none of your business,
don't admit it!
Please don't tell them!
He was just sneaking into backyard,
it's no big deal!
He is no murderer or anything like that
You can spare all these inhuman torture!
He's only a kid!
He doesn't want to betray his friend
If he betrays me today
He'll betray Shaolin Temple tomorrow
Is that too difficult to comprehend!
How can you teach your pupils from now
on?
You say you are moving along with the
modern world!
The words are beautiful but you never
open the cage
You won't give the kid freedom to visit
the backyard!
How can you revolutionize Shaolin Temple
like this?
Please don't torture him anymore
I will take the rest of the spanking
for him
Come on!
I said go ahead!
Don't spank him, don't!
We are even from now on!
Don't torture this kid anymore
باسنم درد میکنه داداش!
Shut your mouth
Wu-Yen
استاد
Why are you here?
I thought it's your shift to cook?
آقای چانگ said
He's been here too long
He said he wants to cook us a meal
He will arrange all vegetarian dishes
for us!
What's that?
It's vegetarian food!
It's Sushi!
Have you tried before?
نه!
آقای چانگ, before you go
I have something to tell you
What is it?
The things you say inside the
Monkey Temple today
I think it's absolutely right
But this doesn't mean I am wrong
Buddha has a saying
Right is wrong, wrong is right
آقای چانگ, do you understand?
نه, I don't
That means whatever you say are all
wrong!
چی؟
You are leaving without settling
Tong Ling's matter?
We Chinese doesn't work like you
American
We follow up from beginning to the end
I am not asking you to stay
But if you decide to stay
It's your own decision!
What are you doing?
Why did you kiss me?
This is our American way of showing
affection
You're not a woman, what is the big deal?
This is even worse, two men kissing and
hugging!
استاد
چی؟
You speak up!
استاد
You tell us to take آقای چانگ's luggage
back to room?
I've told you already
What do you have or embarrass me?
Namonitabhaya!
آقای چانگ
Be careful آقای چانگ, my ass is still
hurting
This is Japanese food, vegetable Tempura!
And this is Sushi, and French fries!
Cheers!
He didn't leave?
He said read this if you are bored
important thing in playing baseball is
personal touch
Do you understand!
بله we do!
Show me the position
Here's your lunch, Miss Mei
Don't let استاد know about this
Leave, leave now
Listen carefully, I'll teach you once
more only
Understand? بله
Show me. چی؟
I teach you once more
OK!
Understand? چی؟
Making fun of me?
Oh my god! Stay away!
Oh! Shit!
Killing 3 monks with one ball
I'm not sick, I'm just exhausted
You read books till dawn, that's why
you're exhausted
Have you ever read this book before
Never. These books are only suitable
for kids
Read it. It's very touching
Take this medicine!
آقای چانگ, hurry up!
Will be in trouble if استاد knows
I'm leaving now!
Swallow it!
Give me back the cover
Good girl
Touching?
Some pages are misssing
Miss Mei
It's my turn today
Use my energy to save my face
1,1,1,1,2,3
4,5,6,7
Take your time, you will be better
than me
Bon Appetite...
Bon Appetite, Ching
What did you say? You said Bon appetite?
بله
Dad and Mom, she said Bon appetite
I am thrilled
We are leaving so soon? Leaving in
three days
بله
You don't want to leave?
Why do you say that?
I'm used to here, I'll miss it
What do you miss most?
My first love experience is like that
of Miss Ching-Ching
both in love with the man who've afraid
to show his affection
These pages in the book
are about how Miss Ching-Ching fells
about Man-keung
She was hoping that Man-keung could
stayed by her side
and to provide her with a cosy family.
I have the same expectation as Ching
That's why I am keeping these few pages
from the book
Hoping that Ching will be able to
see this
and learn what I am hoping for
I'll soon finish the book
I wonder if Ching-ching will get
together
with Man-keung at the end
استاد, it's you
Do you know that آقای چانگ is leaving?
I know he'll leave sooner or later
He's only an ordinary passer by in China
Don't blind yourself with short-term
happiness
Painful memories often come after
I don't want him to leave Shaolin Temple
And left behind some bad memories
for you
Miss Mei
He belongs to the outside world
You would not fit in
And it would be too late to find out!
Moreover, he's been with too many women
He won't stay behind for you
Who is this?
It's me, open up
We need to talk
We can talk likes this
I'm leaving in two days
You don't seem to have friends here
Maybe you want to come to the
States with me?
You want me to go to the States
with you?
If I ask you to stay in China
can you do that for me?
Namomitabhaya
Just shut up, I'll give you four times
more. Just drive!
What do you want?
I don't like to take orders
So how much do you want?
I am a fair person
You cheat me once, I got back to you once
So we are even now
I'll charge according to the meter
You look dried up. I'll take you to a
whore house
Beijing chicks are chubby and white
Mongolia chicks have big boops
If you don't like chicken, I can get you
a cock
You shut up!
Or else I can get you a noisy bitch!
Wait! Stop the car
You want donkey!
Hey! I'm just kidding, man
Are you sure about this?
This donkey has got disease
Wait for me
You are really going all out for it, eh?
Make sure you have double protection!
Who the hell are you?
Hell, Hell, Hell
You are going to hell indeed
He just called in, I think he has arrived
نهtify Captain Chiu!
OK
You should re-arrange your men
Captain Chiu, Mr Wong has arrived
He is waiting for you downstairs
Let's go then. OK
Mr Wong, my room is over there
Mr Wong, please come in
Please
This is the custom documents for the
treasure
When she arrives in Taiwan
We'll pay you the other half of the
money
نه problem
But now I want another ten million U. S
چی؟
Ten million U.S.?
I thought we had a deal
The way I see it
I have to take out Chang Ching in Taiwan
Without causing any suspicion to U.S.
Authority
Plus returning the national treasure to
you guys
So you guys can sell her to another
country
All I got is just over ten million
This doesn't seem to be fair
You must realize
It is possible I can't return to U.S.
After this
It's better to have some saving in the
Bank
What if I say no?
You must bear in mind that
We are all in this together
If you back out now
And the plan is exposed. You'll be in
shit too
Fine
Ten million is nothing
نه
It's more important to have a friend
There are more chances in the future?
Finish it off. بله
Watch out, I'll find a bag
Seal off all exists
Follow me
What's happening?
Back off, back off, nobody is allowed in
I shot him
Who?
Chang...
Give way
نهbody went through any exits
He must be upstairs
Where to?
Shaolin Temple
You are in a pool of blood
I only contracted this taxi
Don't you mess up the cab
خفه شو and drive!
Drive
Listen, you better not die in my cab
You can die outside
Take a look yourself
What's the big deal?
You are stealing stack of blank papers
I told you to get laid!
The middle pages, you idiot! Can't we do
this later?
Somebody help!
همون‌جا وساط
What are you doing here?
He's injured and I helped him
That's none of your business
Out
You think I wanna be here
He's injured
It's bad luck even meeting you
Leave Shaolin Temple immediately
Drive your stupid taxi
How dare you talk to me like that
You two please stop arguing
I'm gonna died of bleeding soon
He's way out of line
Anyway you look at it, I am his senior
colleague
But you failed to give up the 6 carnal
desires
And you indulge in gambling
You don't qualify to be my
senior colleague
نه qualify?
When I cash in you also got a share
You didn't say I'm not qualify
Anyway, استاد has forbidden your entry
to Shaolin Temple
Fine, let's go
Don't leave, don't go
He asked you to leave, not me
Hey, we just went through death valleys
together
How can I leave you now
Don't be so nice to me
Just leave me here at any corner
نه way!
You better put him down so I can move
him inside
Fine, I'll teach you a lesson on behalf
of our استاد
You stupid bald monk
You called me stupid bald monk.
You, long hair bandit
Go to hell!
You bit me
Again. Sure, be my quest!
Oh shit! Great! I got you this time
Give it back to me!
Block him, don't stop me, block him
Kung-chi, stay right here
استاد, catch it... باشه
استاد, here's stick!
Hurry up
You little bugger, you chicken out?
Lost way
You stupid bald monk
Let's fight up here
Whoever falls down deserve to die
Then you'll be the one. I am not scared
You, go to hell!
Good. چی؟
Kung Ching you don't have respect
Betray your استاد and injured the
Abbot today
Betray my استاد?
It's better than you betraying your
country for money
What are you saying?
You team up with Tong Ling in crime
I have the evidence with me
Hiding the national treasure at
Shaolin Temple
Senior استاد
This is a total disgrace to the
Buddhist Region
This is against my will
I was blackmailed by Tong Ling
You know how tricky and cunning he is
And now you disclose everything!
Our استاد has been kidnapped by
Tong Ling
Where is آقای چانگ?
He's in my room
Why is he in your room?
He is sick, Sr. استاد gave him medicine
he is resting now
چی؟ What did you say?
He is sick
Sick?
I come to visit him and he's sick,
what a co-incidence
I suspect he has been to the
Police Headquarters
If only I could match his finger print
on the weapon
You'll have to die before me!
You two come with me
You bring some people to Mei's room
استاد, is he...
It's hard to say
استاد
استاد, is he going to blow...
Blow what?
He couldn't possibly be uninjured
نه finger print on the murderer's weapon
I already know you had saved him with
your admission
If it is not you who did it
How can he possibly be alive?
The fingerprints had proven the
murder's identity
It's Chang Ching
With this evidence
it is easy to indict him of murder
Even if I let him go
The Americans would never leave him
alone
But I need the truth from you
Cos' if anyone else lie to me
I do not care
But if you lie to me
I'll be really upset
You must know
How well I had treated you
at the research institute
Because I really like you a lot
Mr Tong, if you promise you won't hurt
Ching
I'll do whatever you say
How can I heal from the two gun wounds?
When you were unconscious
Miss Mei asked me to use her power to
save you
You should go to see her now
Thanks
If this incident that
cause the old master any danger
Please forgive me
Mei?
I've gone to the bookshop
And I finally finish the whole book
Miss Ching-ching and Hui Man-keung
cannot be together
But I know we won't be like them
You must leave with me
You'll be safe at the States
You are leaving with me tonight
Every single time
I was so happy that we spent nights
under the moon
I can't let go of you
When we arrive at America
We can spend every night under the moon
You'll be happy as ever
He's OK
He's absolutely fine
Why are you so worried?
استاد has heart problem
You have to take him to the hospital
immediately
Why are you so stupid?
The plan will be a failure if I send
him to hospital
The all my effort will be in vain
You should be ashamed of yourself
استاد has done a lot of favors to us
How can you treat him like this
Calm down
I would let you go soon
Only when I get my share of money...
Everything will be back to normal
You're disguising me selling the
national treasure
How can you live up to the country and
its people?
I'm the big bastard
I faked you well, don't I?
Even my sister-in-law can't tell the
difference in bed
You scared me to death
When I finish my job
You can be the police captain again
OK?
Hey, this is fun
Keep a good look at my treasure
You must forgive your brother
Man's life is short
Just like the sound of bell
It will disappear in a glimpse...
Wind Charm
استاد!
Please take care. Please take care
You are a big boy now, don't cry
Take care. You too
استاد
You don't need to look for Miss Mei
Why not?
Cos' I took her away already
You took her away?
Where did you take her?
To Mr Tong's place
They had an agreement
If only Mr Tong agreed not to hurt you
She agreed to let Tong sell her to
anyone
She didn't care about herself
Don't be foolish
Miss Mei had done all this for your
own good
If I leave her like this
I can hardly consider myself a man
Wait a second
What do you want again?
Go now
ممنون
Hope you two can live happily ever after
If only you could find her
کجا داری میری؟ See you tomorrow!
Let's drink!
Let's drink, come over!
Cheers...
What are you doing, don't
Hate these people, pure harassment
Go out and have a look
I said you go and check!
Is everything OK?
Be careful, keep your eye on it!
I think
we can double cross the American...
That will do it
خفه شو
Did you hear something?
نه, nothing! What noise?
The sound from Wind Charm! نهthing at all
Are you sure?
نهthing at all
Go, good!
Bottom's up! Bottom's up!
Chang Ching!
Look out!
Use the back door
Open it
How we gonna do?
Cover me and let's go
Let's battle!
Cover me, cover me
Don't stop, move out!
Charge! Charge!
Don't give up...
Don't move!
How can you get out, brother?
You never have thought of that?
You never know the time to confess
Don't push me! We'll all die together!
Let her go
Look behind you
I know that's a gun behind me
But only if I can save Mei
I won't care about my life!
Don't come near
I'll kill her
I've decided not to go back to the
States
I'll stay in China with you
You're so stupid
We all want to leave China
What can you do here?
I should have said this earlier
I don't know what you're talking about
I need a car to escape
Be quick
Let her go! You want to die
I don't care
Don't move
Do you want to cry?
Ching
You guys protect her
The rest follow me. بله!
Ching
What is that sound? What is happening?
What is that sound?
Wind Charm? Wind Charm?
Namomitabhaya...
من بی‌گناهم, من بی‌گناهم!
من بی‌گناهم!
Namomitabhaya...
Go to Hell!
This is Captain Chiu
This is Captain Kam
How do you do?
If you have any message
Let me go and tell them
What else can I say?
This is the worse for me
I shouldn't have betrayed the country
because of استاد
I know I should go to jail
I'm afraid no one would lead
Shaolin while I'm away
You are truly the eldest monk
Go back and be a leader if you have
the time
نه
When استاد was alive, he didn't allow
me to go back to Shaolin
Maybe when the pupils are out
I'll give them a ride for free
You have to keep your promise then
ممنون!
Don't worry
I don't think I'll have a chance to
say farewell
Anything I can help?
I would like to go out for a while
Captain Chiu
One minute
ممنون!
Do you remember in the end of the book?
I don't believe that
This would happen to us
I'm not sure whether I will be allowed
to stay in China
And I don't know when will I be able
to see you again
But I know whenever I look at the moon
I will remember you
I have something for you
Can we do this one more time
I'm waiting!
I'm waiting...
Mei
I returned to the research institute
for almost 2 years
During this period
My power slowly disappeared without
any reasonable explanation
This spring, the staff of research
institute inform me
That they don't need me anymore!
I finally can try and taste the life of
a normal person
Although I got my freedom
But I am not as happy as before
Maybe it's because I've lost Ching!
I tried to locate Ching through many
different sources
With no positive news
But I believe that he will come and
look for me
Maybe one day, I will meet him again at
the train station
Can you fly with me one more time